MATAS SABALIAUSKAS

ENTRY-LEVEL FRONT-END DEVELOPER



- +370 607 89219
- matas.sabaliauskas@gmail.com
- Vilnius
- in linkedin.com/in/matas-sabaliauskas-9935101b6/

ABOUT ME

I gained most of my job experience is in recruiting but recently I became interested Front-End development. Although I studied on my own at the beginning, I decided to deepen my knowledge by taking a JavaScript course at Vilnius Coding School. I am currently open to new opportunities.

TECHNICAL SKILLS

- Building carcass of website with HTML5
- Styling website using CSS3
- Making website dynamic with JavaScript
- Building website using react.js
- Cutting design from Figma
- Editing illustrations with Adobe Photoshop

EDUCATION

JAVASCRIPT (FRONT-END) COURSES

Vilnius Coding School 2022-06 iki 2022-07 | 140val.

Acquired strong web carcass and styling skills with HTML5 and CSS3 Also I learned how to make website dynamic with JavaScript and react.js.

My final project was graded 10 points: https://github.com/matasz21/VCSbaigiamasis

ORGANIZATIONAL PSYCHOLOGY

Vilnius University 2021-2022

PSYCHOLOGY

Vilnius University 2017-2021

EXPERIENCE

APOLLO GROUP

Recruitment specialist 2022-01 iki 2022-06

TELE₂

Junior talent acquisition specialist 2021-05 iki 2021-12